Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - MISCELLANEOUS (ILLEGIBLE, UNKNOWN, UNSIGNED, FRAGMENTS,ETC.) (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - 12. N.D.N.P. Handwritten note Wm. Lee of Hartwell in the Co. of Bucks Esqr. and Henry Harcourt of Penley in the Co. of Herts Esqr.
INDEX OF DATES
1754 5-37-53
1756 2-14-31
1759 1-1-26; 2-16-15, 16; 5-37-49, 50
1762 3-25-1, 2
1763 3-19-1, 2, 3
1764 3-19-(4-8); 5-32-10
1765 3-19-(9-10)
1767 3-19-11, 12
1768 3-25-3
1771 3-19-13; 3-25-4
1772 3-19-14, 15
1776 3-25-5, 6
1778 3-24-(1-5); 3-25-(8-11); 6-42-43
1779 2-9-35; 3-24-6; 3-25-(12?-14)
1777 3-25-7
1770 5-32-11
1780 2-14-20; 3-24-(7-9); 4-27-1
1781 4-27-2, 3; 5-35-17; 1-1-14; 1-4-9; 1-5-1; 2-14-40; 3-24-10; 3-25-12?; (15-19)
1782 1-4-10, 11; 2-13-21; 3-23-1; 3-25-20, 21; 5-35-18; 5-37-25, 26, 48
1783 1-4-12, 27; 2-11-1; 2-13-22; 3-24-11; 3-25-(22-30)
1784 3-25-(31-40)
1785 1-3-24; 1-4-28; 1-5-47; 2-9-6; 2-16-1, 2, 7, 8, (22-24); 3-25-41, (44-46); 5-35-39
1786 1-3-37, 38; 2-9-36; 2-10-1,2; 2-12-13; 2-13-(23-26), 56; 2-14-1; 2-17-(12-15); 3-18-4, 5; 4-26-(1-9b); 4-27-4, 5; 5-39-1
1787 2-9-8,9; 2-10-(3-7); 2-12-16; 2-13-(27-30), 49, 57; 2-14-3; 2-16-(25-28); 3-18-6; 3-20-1; 3-22-(23-25); 4-26-10; 4-27-6; 5-33-3; 5-37-(2-6); 5-39-2; 6-40-(5-9); 6-42-35
1788 1-1-4, 33, 34; 1-3-23, 42, 43; 1-7-1, 2; 2-9-1; 2-10-(9-19); 2-11-9; 2-13-31, 32 2-16-29a&b, 30; 4-27-(7-11); 5-33-4; 5-35-(2-4), 16; 6-40-10; 6-42-2, 38
1789 1-1-35; 1-3-(16-18), 27, 44, 63; 1-4-(59-73); 2-10-20, 21; 2-13-50; 3-18-(7-11); 3-20-2; 3-22-45; 4-26-(11-16); 4-27-(12-20); 4-31-33, 34; 5-33-30; 5-34-2; 5-35-21, 41; 5-37-39; 5-39-3, 4; 6-40-24; 6-42-31, 33
1790
Jan. 1-5-21; 2-15-2; 2-16-34; 3-20-11; 3-24-12; 5-37-19
Feb. 1-3-51; 1-4-74; 1-5-22, 23; 3-24-13; 6-41-1
Mar. 1-3-25; 1-5-37; 1-7-3; 3-24-13; 5-35-42; 6-42-18
Apr. 3-23-2; 4-26-17; 5-35-43
May 1-4-75; 4-31-39; 6-42-6
June 4-26-18
July [3-24-19], 20; 4-27-21; 5-39-5
Aug. 2-13-58
Sept. 1-7-4; 4-26-19; 5-34-1, 3; 5-39-6
Oct. 1-1-27; 2-10-22; 2-12-1; 6-42-44, 45
Nov. 1-1-28, 29; 1-3-1, 2, 10, 11; 1-4-49; 1-7-5; 2-9-31; 2-12-2a; 2-15-1; 2-20-12; 2-20-13; 4-29-(1-5); 5-39-7
Dec. 1-3-12, 28; 1-4-50; 4-27-22; 4-29-(6-8); 6-42-22
ND 2-9-32, 33
1791
Jan. 1-5-57; 2-14-21, 22; 3-18-12; 3-20-14
Feb. 1-5-24, 58; 1-7-6, 7; 2-14-23, 24; 5-34-4
Mar. 4-27-23; 4-31-40
Apr. 1-5-25
May 2-12-2b; 3-23-3; 5-34-5
June 1-6-1; 3-18-13; 3-20-3; 6-40-(19-21); 6-42-4
July 5-38-1; 5-39-8
Aug. 1-6-2; 1-7-8; 2-14-19
Sept. 1-5-8; 5-39-9
Oct. [1-5-41]; 1-7-9; 2-17-1; 5-39-(10-12); 6-40-22
Nov. 1-4-51; [1-5-(42-44)]; 2-11-3; 2-20-15; 5-39-(13-15)
Dec. [1-5-45]; 5-38-2
ND 1-3-45
1792
Jan. 1-6-3; 1-7-10, 11; 2-14-9; 3-18-14; 3-23-4; 5-34-6, 7, 8; 5-37-8; 5-39-16
Feb. 1-5-9; 2-16-18; 3-18-15, 16; 4-27-24; 5-34-9; 5-38-3; 5-39-(17-20); 6-40-26
Mar. 1-6-4; 2-12-14; 4-31-35; 5-34-10; 5-35-5; 5-37-9; 5-39-21, 22; 6-42-11
Apr. 1-7-12; 5-34-11, 12; 5-35-23
May 2-12-18; 3-23-5; 5-39-23
June 1-5-59; 2-9-10, 11; 2-12-17; 2-13-59; 3-18-17; 5-33-20; 5-34-13; 5-35-(26-28)
July 2-9-12, 13; 2-15-3; 3-18-18; 4-26-20; 5-33-9; 5-35-14; 6-40-27
Aug. 4-27-25, 26; 5-34-14; 6-44-2
Sept.
Oct.
Nov. [2-12-15]; 2-13-52; 5-34-15, 16; 5-37-40, 43; 6-42-24
Dec. 1-4-13, 14; 2-14-10; 5-35-15; 5-37-44
ND 2-9-(3-5); 3-18-19
1793
Jan. 1-3-13; 1-4-15; 1-6-5; 2-13-34; 4-27-27, 28; 5-39-24; 6-41-2
Feb. 1-5-19; 1-6-6; 5-35-29; 5-37-45; 5-38-4; 5-39-25, 26; 6-42-8, 46
Mar. 1-3-29; 2-11-4; 4-26-21; 4-31-18; 5-37-28; 5-39-27, 28
Apr. 1-3-30, 31; 5-38-5
May 5-34-17, 18
June 1-7-13
July 1-7-14; 5-33-13
Aug. 1-7-15, 16
Sept. 1-7-15
Oct. 1-4-1; 1-5-61; 1-7-15, 17; 2-9-38; 3-23-6; 4-27-29
Nov. 1-4-2,3; 5-33-19; 6-41-3
Dec. 1-3-14; 4-27-30; 5-34-19
ND 5-38-6
1794
Jan. 1-1-11; [1-5-27]; 5-39-29
Feb. 1-6-7; 5-39-30; 6-40-4
Mar. 1-5-55; 3-23-7
Apr. 1-6-8; 1-7-18; 5-38-7
May 1-7-19; 4-27-31, 32; 6-42-25
June 1-7-20; 4-26-22, 23; 5-37-13
July [1-3-5]; 2-11-6; 4-26-24, 25; 4-27-33; 5-39-31
Aug. 1-4-52; 3-23-8; 4-26-26
Sept. 1-4-53; 1-7-(21-23); 3-23-9; 4-26-27; 5-34-20
Oct. 1-1-6; 1-3-20; 2-13-35; 3-23-10; 4-26-28; 6-40-14
Nov. 1-7-24, 25; 3-23-11, 12; 4-26-29
Dec. 1-7-26; 3-22-12; 3-23-13; 4-26-30; 5-38-8
ND 3-23-14
1795
Jan. 1-7-27, 28; [2-12-8]; 2-16-(32-33); 3-22-13, 14; 3-24-14; 4-26-(31-33)
Feb. 1-1-12; 2-12-9, 10
Mar. 1-3-9, 46; 1-5-56; 2-12-11; 2-13-36; 2-14-14; 4-26-34; 4-27-34, 35; 4-31-14; 5-38-9; 6-42-29
Apr. 1-7-29, 30; 3-22-15; 3-23-15; 4-26-34; 5-37-29
May 1-7-31, 32; 2-14-2; 2-16-17; 3-22-16; 3-22-27, 28; 3-23-16; 4-26-36; 5-37-30; 5-38-10
June 1-1-16; 1-3-47; 1-5-46; 1-7-(33-36); 2-13-37; 3-22-27, 28; 3-28-17; 4-31-27; 5-35-40; 5-37-31
July 1-2-1; 1-7-(37-40); 3-24-16; 4-26-37; 4-27-36, 37
Aug. 1-7-41; 3-23-18; 4-26-38; 4-27-38, 39; 5-37-32
Sept. 1-2-2; 1-5-60; 1-7-42; 2-9-22, 23; 2-10-8; 5-35-11
Oct. 1-3-21; 2-13-38; 4-26-39, 40; 4-27-40
Nov. 1-4-16; 1-5-39; 1-7-43; 2-11-8; 2-14-11; 3-23-19, 20; 4-26-41; 4-27-41, 42; 5-33-1; 5-37-10, 14,15; 5-38-11, 12
Dec. 1-3-22; 1-7-44; 2-9-(24-27); 2-13-39, 40; 4-31-(19-21); 5-32-6, 7; 5-38-13, 14; 6-42-19
ND [1-2-39]; 5-38-15
1796
Jan.
Feb. 2-12-7; 2-13-41; 2-17-(2-5); 3-20-16, 35; 4-27-(48-51)
Mar. 1-1-5; 1-2-3; 1-3-54, 55; 2-8-1; 2-11-7; 2-13-1, 42,43; 2-14-38; 2-17-6; 4-26-42; 4-27-(52-54); 5-38-16; 5-39-32
Apr. 1-2-4; 1-3-36; 1-5-7, 35; 1-6-9; 2-8-2; 2-9-2; 2-13-(2-5); 3-22-17, 18; 3-22-30, 31; 4-26-43; 4-27-(43a-45); 5-35-12; 5-38-(17-23); 5-39-33
May 2-9-37, 43; 3-22-32; 4-26-44; 4-27-46, 47, 55, 56; 5-39-34; 6-40-30
June 3-20-17; 4-26-45; 4-27-(57-59); 5-38-24; 5-39-35, 36
July [1-3-65]; 1-4-4; 2-8-3; 2-9-17, 18; 2-13-6, 44, 45, [60]; 3-22-46; 5-37-33; 6-41-4, 5
Aug. 2-8-4; 2-17-7; 4-26-46; 5-33-18, 28; 6-41-6, 7
Sept. 1-4-31; 2-8-5; 2-9-21; 2-14-7; 4-27-60; 6-41-8, 9; 6-42-30
Oct. 1-1-17; 1-2-5; 2-8-6, 7; 2-13-7; 3-22-11, 33, 34; 4-26-47; 5-39-37
Nov. 1-2-(6-9); 1-3-56; 1-4-32, 33; 1-6-10; 2-13-46; 3-22-35
Dec. 1-2-10; 1-5-36; 1-6-11, 17; s-8-8, 9; 2-13-47; 2-14-12; 4-26-(48-50); 5-34-22; 5-35-44; 5-38-25
ND 5-35-37, 38; 5-39-38; 6-40-31
1797
Jan. 1-2-11; 1-4-34; 2-12-19; 2-13-48; 3-18-20, 21; 3-22-36; 4-28-1; 5-34-23; 5-35-45; 5-39-39
Feb. 1-3-40; 1-4-35; 1-5-29; 1-6-12; 2-8-10; 2-14-43; 3-20-(18-20); 4-28-2, 3; 5-39-40
Mar. 1-3-41; 1-4-17; 1-4-36, 37; 1-5-26, 30; 1-6-(14-16); 2-8-11; 2-9-34; 3-20-21, 22; 3-22-37, 44; 4-28-4, 5; 5-32-7b; 5-33-10, 14, 29; 5-35-31
Apr. 3-18-1, 2; 3-22-19, 20; 4-26-(52-54); 4-28-6; 5-39-41
May 1-2-12, 13; 1-3-57; 1-4-38; 1-5-62; 2-8-12; 2-11-5; 2-14-34; 3-20-(23-25); 6-40-29
June 1-2-(15-20); 1-6-13; 2-8-13; 2-16-9; 6-40-17, 18; 6-42-17
July 1-2-21, 22; 1-5-16, 17; 2-8-14
Aug. 2-8-15, 16; 3-23-21; 5-33-7; 5-35-46; 5-39-42
Sept. 2-8-17; 2-14-39; 3-18-35; 3-23-22; 4-28-7
Oct. 2-16-10, 11; 6-40-12
Nov. 2-14-29; 3-22-(38-40); 4-28-8, 9
Dec. 1-1-36; 1-3-48; 6-42-12
ND 4-28-10, 11
1798
Jan. 1-4-39; 2-8-18; 3-20-26; 3-22-8; 4-28-12; 5-33-5; 6-42-3
Feb. 1-1-32, 37; 1-3-6, 7, 58; 1-4-40, 41, 54; 1-5-31; 2-8-(19-21); 2-12-3, 12; 2-13-8; 3-21-1, 2; 3-22-42; 4-26-55; 4-28-13; 5-37-46
Mar. 1-4-42,43; 2-8-22; 2-9-15; 3-21-3; 3-22-9; 5-33-6; 5-35-13, 22; 5-38-26
Apr. 1-3-8; 1-4-5; 2-8-23; 6-42-10, 13
May 1-2-23; 2-13-61; 2-16-21; 3-20-9
June 2-13-62; 5-33-25; 6-40-1; 6-42-14, 16
July 2-8-24; 2-13-9, 10; 3-20-27; 4-28-14
Aug. 2-8-25; 2-14-8; 4-26-56
Sept. 2-8-26; 2-14-30; 3-20-28; 4-26-57; 4-31- 2; 6-42-5
Oct. 2-16-13; 4-28-15; 6-42-28
Nov. 2-8-27; 2-12-20; 3-18-36; 5-35-34; 6-42-27
Dec. 1-2-24; 2-13-11; 12; 2-16-14; 5-33-2a; 5-34-24; 5-38-27; 5-39-(43-46); 6-41-10, 11; 6-42-37; 6-43-1
ND 1-4-44; 2-13-63
1799
Jan. 1-2-25; 1-5-12, 20, 21; 4-28-16; 4-31-8, 37; 5-34-25; 5-35-32; 5-39-47; 6-41-12; 6-43-(2-4)
Feb. 1-2-26, 27; 1-3-32, 33; 2-8-28, 29; 3-21-9; 4-28-(17-19); 4-31-9; 5-34-26; 5-37-16, 41; 5-39-48, 49; 6-40-13; 6-41-13, 14
Mar. 1-1-7, 8; 1-3-34; 2-8-30; 2-13-13, 14; 2-14-4, 5; 4-28-20, 21; 5-32-2, 3; 5-35-33
Apr. 3-21-4; 4-28-22, 23; 5-33-26; 5-38-28; 6-41-15; 6-42-42; 6-43-5
May 1-3-4; 1-4-6; 1-5-40; 2-9-16; 2-11-10; 2-13-15; 2-16-3; 2-17-8a, 8b; 4-31-30; 5-37-37; 5-39-50, 51; 6-40-15; 6-42-7, 40
June 1-2-(28-30); 1-5-6; 2-9-14, 19; 2-12-4; 2-13-16, 17; 3-20-29; 4-28-24, 25; 4-31-41; 5-38-29; 5-39-52, 53; 6-40-15; 6-42-22
July 1-4-18; 2-14-13, 32; 3-24-17; 5-32-9; 5-34-27
Aug. 1-3-52; 2-8-31; 3-23-23, 24; 4-28-26; 4-31-15; 5-33-16; 5-36-2; 5-37-20, 51
Sept. 2-11-11; 2-13-18; 3-22-6; 3-23-(24-26); 4-28-27, 28; 4-31-1; 5-36-3, 4; 5-37-54; 6-41-16; 6-42-15
Oct. 1-1-19; 1-2-31, 32; 1-5-15; 2-9-20; 2-13-19; 3-20-7; 3-21-5; 4-28-29; 5-35-6; 5-36-(5-9)
Nov. 1-2-33, 34; 1-4-19, 20; 1-5-2, 13, 14; 2-8-32; 2-14-33; 2-16-12; 4-28-(30-31b); 4-31-3, 4, 16; 5-34-28; 5-35-7; 5-36-10, 11; 6-42-9
Dec. 1-5-3; 2-8-33; 3-20-30; 3-21-6; 3-23-27; 4-28-32, 33; 4-31-(5-7); 5-33-2b; 5-33-11; 5-36-12, 13; 5-39-(54-58)
ND 1-5-32; 4-28-34; 5-34-(29-31)
1800
Jan. 1-2-35; 2-14-35; 3-20-31; 3-23-(28-31); 4-28-35a, 35b; 4-31-23, 24; 5-33-17, 24; 5-36-(14-16); 5-37-7, 24; 6-43-(6-9)
Feb. 1-4-7; 4-28-36; 4-30-1; 5-39-(59-62)
Mar. 1-5-33; 3-22-41; 4-28-37; 4-30-2; 5-35-9; 5-36-17; 5-37-21; 6-42-26; 6-43-10
Apr. 1-5-5, (52-54); 2-13-64; 2-14-41,42; 2-16-19,20; 3-20-10; 3-21-7; 4-31-17; 5-35-8; 5-36-18; 5-37-11,22,38
May 1-2-36, 37; 1-3-53; 1-4-(21-25a); 1-5-10; 2-8-34; 2-9-7; 5-33-12; 5-35-10; 5-36-(19-21)
June 3-20-5; 4-28-38
July 4-28-(39-41)
Aug. 1-4-25b
Sept.
Oct. 6-44-5
Nov. 1-3-49; 2-14-36, 37; 3-22-10; 4-28-(42-45); 4-31-10; 6-40-2; 6-44-6
Dec. 4-28-(46-48); 6-40-3
ND 1-3-50; 2-16-(4-6); 3-23-32; 5-35-19, 20; 6-44-3, 4, 9
1801
Jan. 4-30-3; 4-31-11; 5-36-22
Feb. 2-14-26, 27; 2-16-35; 3-20-8; 3-22-(2-4); 5-32-1; 5-37-52
Mar. 1-5-38; 2-14-15; 4-30-4
May 4-30-5,6
Oct. 4-30-7; 4-31-12
1802
Jan. 3-23-33; 4-30-8
Apr. 4-30-9, 10
Sept. 2-14-(16-18)
1804
Aug. 2-13-53
1805
Feb. 2-13-54
1807
May 2-13-55
1808
Feb. 4-31-26
1818
Mar. 3-23-34
1836
June 5-33-8